<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Home</title>
    <link>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Carter J. Bastian</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CARTER.README</title>
      <link>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/carter_readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/carter_readme/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Carter! If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, you&amp;rsquo;re probably working with me or wondering what it would be like to work with me! The purpose of this doc is to give you some context on what I&amp;rsquo;m like as a coworker and as a person.
This was inspired by the trend of manager READMEs that was floating around hacker news a while back. I&amp;rsquo;m writing this in the hopes that the trend takes off more broadly &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;d love to have a little guide to the working styles of everyone you work closely with!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Addition by Subtraction</title>
      <link>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/addition-by-subtraction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/addition-by-subtraction/</guid>
      <description>Andy: [chuckles] Addition by subtraction.
Michael: What does that even mean? That is impossible.
Andy: Mmmm. Yeah you&amp;rsquo;re right.
Michael: But, there is some good news. Oscar is back. Addition by addition
 The Problem with Resolutions I love New Years Eve. It&amp;rsquo;s my favorite of all holidays! Other holidays celebrate bunnies, or monsters, or the systemic exploitation of indigenous people, or Jesus Christ&amp;rsquo;s kind-of birthday[1], but not New Years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Untangling Khan Academy&#39;s Python Codebase</title>
      <link>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/adr13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/adr13/</guid>
      <description>[ This article is cross-posted from Khan Academy&amp;rsquo;s engineering blog. You can see the original here ]
The previous posts about The Great Khan Academy Python Refactor of 2017 and Also 2018 answered two questions: why and how did we refactor all of our Python code? In this post, I want to look closer at a major goal of this project: cleaning up dependencies between parts of our Python codebase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recycling Vim Macros</title>
      <link>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/saved-macros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carterjbastian.github.io/post/saved-macros/</guid>
      <description>Vim macros are neat[1]. The ability to write, store, and repeat arbitrary operations by doing them in the editor once is one of the primary reasons I use vim for (almost) everything I write.
Lint errors[2], on the other hand, are not neat.
In the project my team has been working at Khan Academy for the past few months, we&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a lot of code reorganization and moving files around.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>